A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1947-1951 FA759
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1947
  - Finland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 02.1947/787.E
    - Finland, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2637)
  - Finland - Social Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/787.S
    - Finland, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2637)
  - Lithuania, 1947; 02.1947/788
    - Lithuania, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2637)
  - Poland, 1947; 02.1947/789
    - Poland, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2638)
  - Poland - Medical Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/789.A
    - Poland, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2639)
  - Poland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 02.1947/789.E
    - Poland, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2639)
  - Poland - Health Services, 1947; 02.1947/789.K
    - Poland, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2639)
  - Poland - Public Health Education, 1947; 02.1947/789.L
    - Poland, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2639)
  - Poland - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 02.1947/789.R
    - Poland, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2639)
  - Poland - Social Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/789.S
    - Poland, 1947 (Box 391, Folder 2639)
  - Spain, 1947; 02.1947/795
  - Not Used, 02.1947/795-391
  - Spain - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 02.1947/795.R
  - Not Used, 02.1947/795.R-391
  - Sweden, 1947; 02.1947/800
    - Sweden, 1947 (Box 392, Folder 2640)
  - Sweden - Medical Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/800.A
    - Sweden, 1947 (Box 392, Folder 2641)
  - Sweden - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 02.1947/800.E
    - Sweden, 1947 (Box 392, Folder 2641)
  - Sweden - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 02.1947/800.R
    - Sweden, 1947 (Box 392, Folder 2641)
  - Sweden - Social Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/800.S
    - Sweden, 1947 (Box 392, Folder 2641)
  - Switzerland, 1947; 02.1947/803
    - Switzerland, 1947 (Box 392, Folder 2642)
  - Switzerland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 02.1947/803.E
    - Switzerland, 1947 (Box 392, Folder 2643)
  - Switzerland - Social Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/803.S
    - Switzerland, 1947 (Box 392, Folder 2643)
  - Near East, 1947; 02.1947/804
  - Near East - Humanities and Arts, 1947; 02.1947/804.R
    - Near East, 1947 (Box 392, Folder 2643)
  - Turkey, 1947; 02.1947/805
    - Turkey, 1947 (Box 392, Folder 2643)
  - Turkey - Malaria, 1947; 02.1947/805.I
    - Turkey, 1947 (Box 392, Folder 2643)
  - Cypress, 1947; 02.1947/809
    - Cypress, 1947 (Box 392, Folder 2643)
  - Israel, 1947; 02.1947/825
    - Israel, 1947 (Box 392, Folder 2643)
  - Lebanon, 1947; 02.1947/833
    - Lebanon, 1947 (Box 392, Folder 2643)
  - Lebanon - Medical Sciences, 1947; 02.1947/833.A
    - Lebanon, 1947 (Box 392, Folder 2643)
  - Lebanon - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1947; 02.1947/833.E
    - Lebanon, 1947 (Box 392, Folder 2643)
- General Correspondence, 1948
  - International, 1948; 02.1948/100
    - Staff - International - Aitken, Thomas H.G. - Anderson, Charles R., 1948 (Box 392, Folder 2644)
    - Staff - International - Anderson, Richmond K., 1948 (Box 392, Folder 2645)
    - Staff - International - Balfour, M.C., 1948 (Box 392, Folder 2646)
    - Staff - International - Bates, Marston, 1948 (Box 393, Folder 2647)
    - Staff - International - Belknap, Chauncey - Bevier, George, 1948 (Box 393, Folder 2648)
    - Staff - International - Buchanan, Norman S. - Bugher, John C., 1948 (Box 393, Folder 2649)
    - Staff - International - Burden, Robert P., 1948 (Box 393, Folder 2650)
    - Staff - International - Carr, Henry P., 1948 (Box 393, Folder 2651)
    - Staff - International - Carter, Joseph C., 1948 (Box 393, Folder 2652)
    - Staff - International - Causey, O.R. - Chadwell, H. Marshall - Clarke, P.H. - Copley, Cecil G. - Crowell, F. Elizabeth, 1948 (Box 393, Folder 2653)
    - Staff - International - D'Arms, F.E., 1948 (Box 394, Folder 2654)
    - Staff - International - Debevoise, Thomas M., 1948 (Box 394, Folder 2655)
    - Staff - International - Diplomatic Service - (A-Z) - Dyer, Brian R., 1948 (Box 394, Folder 2656)
    - Staff - International - Elmendorf, John E., 1948 (Box 394, Folder 2657)
    - Staff - International - Fahs, Charles B., 1948 (Box 394, Folder 2658)
    - Staff - International - Fosdick, Raymond B. - Correspondence - Memos, 1948 (Box 394, Folder 2659)
    - Staff - International - Fox, John P., 1948 (Box 394, Folder 2660)
    - Staff - International - Grant, John B. - 1, 1948 (Box 394, Folder 2661)
    - Staff - International - Grant, John B. - 2, 1948 (Box 395, Folder 2662)
    - Staff - International - Hackett, Lewis W., 1948 (Box 395, Folder 2663)
    - Staff - International - Hackett, Lewis W., 1948 (Box 395, Folder 2664)
    - Staff - International - Hahn, Richard G. - Hayes, Guy S., 1948 (Box 395, Folder 2665)
    - Staff - International - Hill, Rolla B., 1948 (Box 395, Folder 2666)
    - Staff - International - Hirst, Esther Mary, 1948 (Box 395, Folder 2667)
    - Staff - International - Hughes, Thomas P., 1948 (Box 395, Folder 2668)
    - Staff - International - Information Exchange, 1948 (Box 396, Folder 2669)
    - Staff - International - International - (A-Z), 1948 (Box 396, Folder 2670)
    - Staff - International - Janney, John H., 1948 (Box 396, Folder 2671)
    - Staff - International - Johnson, Harold N. - Kendrick, John F. - Kerr, J. Austin, 1948 (Box 396, Folder 2672)
    - Staff - International - Kitchen, S.F. - Kittredge, T.B., 1948 (Box 396, Folder 2673)
    - Staff - International - Lambert, Robert A., 1948 (Box 396, Folder 2674)
    - Staff - International - Leach, Charles N., 1948 (Box 396, Folder 2675)
    - Staff - International - Lennette, Edwin H. - Logan, John A., 1948 (Box 397, Folder 2676)
    - Staff - International - McCoy, O.R., 1948 (Box 397, Folder 2677)
    - Staff - International - McIntosh, W.A., 1948 (Box 397, Folder 2678)
    - Staff - International - Magoon, E.H., 1948 (Box 397, Folder 2679)
    - Staff - International - Maier, John, 1948 (Box 397, Folder 2680)
    - Staff - International - Maier, John, 1948 (Box 397, Folder 2681)
    - Staff - International - Mailing Lists, 1948 (Box 398, Folder 2682)
    - Staff - International - Milam, D.F., 1948 (Box 398, Folder 2683)
    - Staff - International - Miller, H.M., 1948 (Box 398, Folder 2684)
    - Staff - International - Morals and Ethics, 1948 (Box 398, Folder 2685)
    - Staff - International - Noll, Anna Mary, 1948 (Box 398, Folder 2686)
    - Staff - International - Oliver, Wade W., 1948 (Box 398, Folder 2687)
    - Staff - International - Pan American Institute of Geography and History, 1948 (Box 398, Folder 2688)
    - Staff - International - Paul, J. Harland - Payne, George C., 1948 (Box 398, Folder 2689)
    - Staff - International - Peterson, O.L., 1948 (Box 399, Folder 2690)
    - Staff - International - Plague - Pomerat, Gerard R. - Psychiatry, 1948 (Box 399, Folder 2691)
    - Staff - International - Putnam, Persis - Rhind, Flora - Rickard, E.R., 1948 (Box 399, Folder 2692)
    - Staff - International - Russell, Paul F., 1948 (Box 399, Folder 2693)
    - Staff - International - Smith, Hugh H., 1948 (Box 399, Folder 2694)
    - Staff - International - Smithburn, Kenneth C., 1948 (Box 399, Folder 2695)
    - Staff - International - Stevens, David H., 1948 (Box 399, Folder 2696)
    - Staff - International - Strode, George K., 1948 (Box 400, Folder 2697)
    - Staff - International - Taylor, R.M., 1948 (Box 400, Folder 2698)
    - Staff - International - Tennant, Mary Elizabeth, 1948 (Box 400, Folder 2699)
    - Staff - International - Tennant, Mary Elizabeth, 1948 (Box 400, Folder 2700)
    - Staff - International - Theiler, Max - Thompson, Norma S., 1948 (Box 400, Folder 2701)
    - Staff - International - United Nations - (A-Z), 1948 (Box 400, Folder 2702)
    - Staff - International - UNESCO, 1948 (Box 400, Folder 2703)
    - Staff - International - UNESCO - (A-E), 1948 (Box 401, Folder 2704)
    - Staff - International - UNESCO - Educational Reconstruction, 1948 (Box 401, Folder 2705)
    - Staff - International - UNESCO - (F-Z), 1948 (Box 401, Folder 2706)
    - Staff - International - UNESCO - (F-Z), 1948 (Box 401, Folder 2706)
    - Staff - International - United Nations - Fellowships, 1948 (Box 401, Folder 2707)
    - Staff - International - United Nations - World Health Organization, 1948 (Box 401, Folder 2708)
    - Staff - International - Varley, Margaret L., 1948 (Box 401, Folder 2709)
    - Staff - International - Warren, Andrew J., 1948 (Box 401, Folder 2710)
    - Staff - International - Watson, Robert Briggs, 1948 (Box 401, Folder 2711)
    - Staff - International - Watson, Robert Briggs, 1948 (Box 402, Folder 2712)
    - Staff - International - Watson, Robert Briggs, 1948 (Box 402, Folder 2713)
    - Staff - International - Weaver, Warren, 1948 (Box 402, Folder 2714)
    - Staff - International - Weir, John M., 1948 (Box 402, Folder 2715)
    - Staff - International - Weir, John M., 1948 (Box 402, Folder 2716)
    - Staff - International - Wells, Clifford W. - Wheeler, C.M. - Whitman, Loring, - Willits, Joseph H., 1948 (Box 402, Folder 2717)
    - Staff - International - Wilson, D. B., 1948 (Box 403, Folder 2718)
    - Staff - International - Worth, C. Brooke, 1948 (Box 403, Folder 2719)
    - Staff - International - Miscellaneous - (A-Z), 1948 (Box 403, Folder 2720)
    - Staff - International - Miscellaneous - (A-Z), 1948 (Box 403, Folder 2721)
    - Staff - International - Miscellaneous - (A-Z), 1948 (Box 403, Folder 2722)
    - Staff - International - Miscellaneous - (A-Z), 1948 (Box 403, Folder 2723)
  - International - Nursing, 1948; 02.1948/100.C
    - Staff - International, 1948 (Box 404, Folder 2724)
  - International - Malaria, 1948; 02.1948/100.I
    - Staff - International, 1948 (Box 404, Folder 2724)
  - International - Yellow Fever, 1948; 02.1948/100.O
    - Staff - International, 1948 (Box 404, Folder 2724)
  - International - Social Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/100.S
    - Staff - International, 1948 (Box 404, Folder 2724)
  - United States, 1948; 02.1948/200
    - United States - (A-Ama), 1948 (Box 404, Folder 2725)
    - United States - (American A-Z), 1948 (Box 404, Folder 2726)
    - United States - (American A-Z), 1948 (Box 404, Folder 2727)
    - United States - (American A-Z), 1948 (Box 404, Folder 2728)
    - United States - (American A-Z), 1948 (Box 404, Folder 2729)
    - United States - (American A-Z), 1948 (Box 404, Folder 2730)
    - United States - (Am-Az), 1948 (Box 405, Folder 2731)
    - United States - (B-Bz), 1948 (Box 405, Folder 2732)
    - United States - (B-Bz), 1948 (Box 405, Folder 2733)
    - United States - (C-Car), 1948 (Box 405, Folder 2734)
    - United States - (C-Car), 1948 (Box 405, Folder 2735)
    - United States - Carter and Jones, 1948 (Box 405, Folder 2736)
    - United States - Carter and Jones, 1948 (Box 405, Folder 2737)
    - United States - (Cat-Cl), 1948 (Box 406, Folder 2738)
    - United States - (Co-Com), 1948 (Box 406, Folder 2739)
    - United States - (Con-Cz), 1948 (Box 406, Folder 2740)
    - United States - (D-De), 1948 (Box 406, Folder 2741)
    - United States - (Di-Dz), 1948 (Box 406, Folder 2742)
    - United States - (E-Ez), 1948 (Box 406, Folder 2743)
    - United States - Eurasia Research Institute - (proposed), 1948 (Box 407, Folder 2744)
    - United States - Er-2 - Copy 1 - (Report), 1948 (Box 407, Folder 2745)
    - United States - (F), 1948 (Box 407, Folder 2746)
    - United States - (Ga-Gz), 1948 (Box 407, Folder 2747)
    - United States - (Ga-Gz), 1948 (Box 407, Folder 2748)
    - United States - (Ha), 1948 (Box 407, Folder 2749)
    - United States - Harvard University - (A-B), 1948 (Box 408, Folder 2750)
    - United States - Harvard University - Business Administration, 1948 (Box 408, Folder 2751)
    - United States - Harvard University - Business Administration, 1948 (Box 408, Folder 2752)
    - United States - Harvard University - (C-L), 1948 (Box 408, Folder 2753)
    - United States - Harvard University - (M-Z), 1948 (Box 408, Folder 2754)
    - United States - Harvard University - World School of Law, 1948 (Box 408, Folder 2755)
    - United States - (He), 1948 (Box 409, Folder 2756)
    - United States - (Hi-Hz), 1948 (Box 409, Folder 2757)
    - United States - (I-In), 1948 (Box 409, Folder 2758)
    - United States - (In-Iz), 1948 (Box 409, Folder 2759)
    - United States - (J-K), 1948 (Box 409, Folder 2760)
    - United States - (J-K), 1948 (Box 409, Folder 2761)
    - United States - (L), 1948 (Box 410, Folder 2762)
    - United States - (Ma-Mar), 1948 (Box 410, Folder 2763)
    - United States - (Mas-Mi), 1948 (Box 410, Folder 2764)
    - United States - (Mo-Mz), 1948 (Box 410, Folder 2765)
    - United States - (Na), 1948 (Box 410, Folder 2766)
    - United States - (National A-Z), 1948 (Box 410, Folder 2767)
    - United States - (Ne-Nz), 1948 (Box 411, Folder 2768)
    - United States - (O), 1948 (Box 411, Folder 2769)
    - United States - (Pa-Pe), 1948 (Box 411, Folder 2770)
    - United States - (Ph-Po), 1948 (Box 411, Folder 2771)
    - United States - (Pr-Ps), 1948 (Box 411, Folder 2772)
    - United States - (Pu-Pz), 1948 (Box 411, Folder 2773)
    - United States - (Q-Ri), 1948 (Box 411, Folder 2774)
    - United States - (Ro-Rz), 1948 (Box 412, Folder 2775)
    - United States - (Sa-Sc), 1948 (Box 412, Folder 2776)
    - United States - (Se-So), 1948 (Box 412, Folder 2777)
    - United States - (Sp-Sz), 1948 (Box 412, Folder 2778)
    - United States - (T), 1948 (Box 412, Folder 2779)
    - United States - Unitarian Service Committee, 1948 (Box 412, Folder 2780)
    - United States - (United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Administration - United Service to China, Inc.), 1948 (Box 413, Folder 2781)
    - United States - (United States: A-O), 1948 (Box 413, Folder 2782)
    - United States - (United States: A-O), 1948 (Box 413, Folder 2783)
    - United States - (United States: PHS), 1948 (Box 413, Folder 2784)
    - United States - (United States: R-Z), 1948 (Box 413, Folder 2785)
    - United States - (Universities), 1948 (Box 413, Folder 2786)
    - United States - (V), 1948 (Box 413, Folder 2787)
    - United States - (Wa), 1948 (Box 413, Folder 2788)
    - United States - (We-Wi), 1948 (Box 414, Folder 2789)
    - United States - (Wo-Wz), 1948 (Box 414, Folder 2790)
    - United States - (X-Z), 1948 (Box 414, Folder 2791)
  - United States - Medical Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/200.A
  - Not Used, 02.1948/200.A-414
  - United States - Nursing, 1948; 02.1948/200.C
    - United States, 1948 (Box 414, Folder 2793)
  - United States - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1948; 02.1948/200.D
    - United States, 1948 (Box 414, Folder 2793)
  - United States - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 02.1948/200.E
    - United States, 1948 (Box 414, Folder 2793)
  - United States - Declinations, 1948; 02.1948/200.F
    - United States, 1948 (Box 414, Folder 2793)
  - United States - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 02.1948/200.R
    - United States - (A-M), 1948 (Box 414, Folder 2794)
    - United States - (N-Z), 1948 (Box 415, Folder 2795)
  - United States - Social Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/200.S
    - United States - (A-Z), 1948 (Box 415, Folder 2796)
    - United States - (A-Z), 1948 (Box 415, Folder 2797)
  - California, 1948; 02.1948/205
    - California - (A-S), 1948 (Box 415, Folder 2798)
    - California - University of California - (A-Z), 1948 (Box 415, Folder 2799)
  - California - Medical Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/205.A
    - California, 1948 (Box 415, Folder 2800)
  - California - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 02.1948/205.R
    - California, 1948 (Box 415, Folder 2800)
  - California - Social Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/205.S
    - California, 1948 (Box 415, Folder 2800)
  - Colorado, 1948; 02.1948/207
  - Colorado - Medical Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/207.A
    - Colorado, 1948 (Box 416, Folder 2801)
  - Colorado - Social Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/207.S
    - Colorado, 1948 (Box 416, Folder 2801)
  - Connecticut, 1948; 02.1948/208
    - Connecticut, 1948 (Box 416, Folder 2801)
  - Connecticut - Nursing, 1948; 02.1948/208.C
    - Connecticut, 1948 (Box 416, Folder 2801)
  - Florida, 1948; 02.1948/211
    - Florida, 1948 (Box 416, Folder 2801)
  - Georgia, 1948; 02.1948/212
    - Georgia, 1948 (Box 416, Folder 2801)
  - Hawaii, 1948; 02.1948/214
    - Hawaii, 1948 (Box 416, Folder 2801)
  - Illinois, 1948; 02.1948/216
    - Illinois, 1948 (Box 416, Folder 2802)
    - Illinois - University of Chicago, 1948 (Box 416, Folder 2803)
  - Illinois - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 02.1948/216.R
    - Illinois, 1948 (Box 416, Folder 2804)
  - Indiana, 1948; 02.1948/217
    - Indiana, 1948 (Box 416, Folder 2804)
  - Kentucky, 1948; 02.1948/220
    - Kentucky, 1948 (Box 416, Folder 2804)
  - Louisiana, 1948; 02.1948/221
    - Louisiana, 1948 (Box 416, Folder 2804)
  - Louisiana - Medical Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/221.A
    - Louisiana, 1948 (Box 416, Folder 2804)
  - Massachusetts, 1948; 02.1948/224
    - Massachusetts, 1948 (Box 416, Folder 2805)
  - Massachusetts - Medical Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/224.A
    - Massachusetts, 1948 (Box 416, Folder 2805)
  - Michigan, 1948; 02.1948/225
    - MIchigan, 1948 (Box 416, Folder 2806)
  - Mississippi, 1948; 02.1948/227
    - Mississippi, 1948 (Box 416, Folder 2806)
  - Missouri, 1948; 02.1948/228
    - Missouri, 1948 (Box 416, Folder 2806)
  - New York, 1948; 02.1948/235
    - New York, 1948 (Box 416, Folder 2806)
  - New York - Humanities, 1948; 02.1948/235.R
    - New York, 1948 (Box 416, Folder 2806)
  - North Carolina, 1948; 02.1948/236
    - North Carolina, 1948 (Box 416, Folder 2806)
  - Ohio, 1948; 02.1948/238
    - Ohio, 1948 (Box 416, Folder 2806)
  - Oregon, 1948; 02.1948/240
    - Oregon, 1948 (Box 416, Folder 2806)
  - Pennsylvania, 1948; 02.1948/241
    - Pennsylvania, 1948 (Box 416, Folder 2807)
  - Philippines, 1948; 02.1948/242
    - Philippines, 1948 (Box 417, Folder 2808)
  - Philippines - Nursing, 1948; 02.1948/242.C
    - Philippines, 1948 (Box 417, Folder 2808)
  - Philippines - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 02.1948/242.E
    - Philippines, 1948 (Box 417, Folder 2808)
  - Philippines - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 02.1948/242.R
    - Philippines, 1948 (Box 417, Folder 2808)
  - Puerto Rico, 1948; 02.1948/243
    - Puerto Rico, 1948 (Box 417, Folder 2809)
  - Puerto Rico - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 02.1948/243.R
    - Puerto Rico, 1948 (Box 417, Folder 2809)
  - Rhode Island, 1948; 02.1948/244
    - Rhode Island, 1948 (Box 417, Folder 2810)
  - Tennessee, 1948; 02.1948/248
    - Tennessee, 1948 (Box 417, Folder 2811)
  - Texas, 1948; 02.1948/249
    - Texas, 1948 (Box 417, Folder 2811)
  - Virginia, 1948; 02.1948/252
    - Virginia, 1948 (Box 417, Folder 2811)
  - Virginia - Medical Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/252.A
    - Virginia, 1948 (Box 417, Folder 2811)
  - Washington, 1948; 02.1948/253
    - Washington, 1948 (Box 417, Folder 2811)
  - Wisconsin, 1948; 02.1948/255
    - Wisconsin, 1948 (Box 417, Folder 2811)
  - Wisconsin - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1948; 02.1948/255.D
    - Wisconsin, 1948 (Box 417, Folder 2811)
  - South America, 1948; 02.1948/300
    - South America - Administration, 1948 (Box 417, Folder 2812)
    - South America - Administration, 1948 (Box 417, Folder 2813)
    - South America, 1948 (Box 417, Folder 2814)
  - South America - Medical Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/300.A
    - South America, 1948 (Box 417, Folder 2814)
  - South America - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1948; 02.1948/300.D
    - South America, 1948 (Box 417, Folder 2814)
  - South America - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 02.1948/300.E
    - South America, 1948 (Box 417, Folder 2814)
  - South America - Social Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/300.S
    - South America, 1948 (Box 417, Folder 2814)
  - Argentina, 1948; 02.1948/301
    - Argentina, 1948 (Box 417, Folder 2815)
  - Argentina - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 02.1948/301.E
    - Argentina, 1948 (Box 417, Folder 2815)
  - Argentina - Yellow Fever, 1948; 02.1948/301.O
    - Argentina, 1948 (Box 417, Folder 2815)
  - Bolivia, 1948; 02.1948/303
    - Bolivia, 1948 (Box 418, Folder 2816)
  - Brazil, 1948; 02.1948/305
    - Brazil - (A-Z), 1948 (Box 418, Folder 2817)
    - Brazil - (A-Z), 1948 (Box 418, Folder 2818)
  - Brazil - Nursing, 1948; 02.1948/305.C
    - Brazil, 1948 (Box 418, Folder 2819)
  - Brazil - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 02.1948/305.E
    - Brazil, 1948 (Box 418, Folder 2819)
  - Brazil - Malaria, 1948; 02.1948/305.I
  - Brazil - Respiratory Diseases, 1948; 02.1948/305.M
    - Brazil, 1948 (Box 418, Folder 2819)
  - Brazil - Yellow Fever, 1948; 02.1948/305.O
    - Brazil, 1948 (Box 418, Folder 2819)
  - Brazil - Tuberculosis, 1948; 02.1948/305.T
  - Brazil, 1948 (Box 418, Folder 2819)
  - Chile, 1948; 02.1948/309
    - Chili, 1948 (Box 418, Folder 2820)
  - Chile - Medical Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/309.A
    - Chili, 1948 (Box 418, Folder 2820)
  - Chile - Nursing, 1948; 02.1948/309.C
    - Chili, 1948 (Box 418, Folder 2820)
  - Chile - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 02.1948/309.E
    - Chili, 1948 (Box 418, Folder 2820)
  - Chile - Social Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/309.S
    - Chili, 1948 (Box 418, Folder 2820)
  - Colombia, 1948; 02.1948/311
    - Colombia, 1948 (Box 418, Folder 2821)
  - Colombia - Medical Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/311.A
    - Colombia, 1948 (Box 418, Folder 2821)
  - Colombia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1948; 02.1948/311.D
    - Colombia, 1948 (Box 418, Folder 2821)
  - Colombia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 02.1948/311.E
    - Colombia, 1948 (Box 418, Folder 2821)
  - Costa Rica, 1948; 02.1948/313
    - Costa Rica, 1948 (Box 418, Folder 2822)
  - Cuba, 1948; 02.1948/315
    - Cuba, 1948 (Box 418, Folder 2822)
  - Ecuador, 1948; 02.1948/317
    - Ecuador, 1948 (Box 418, Folder 2822)
  - Ecuador - Medical Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/317.A
    - Ecuador, 1948 (Box 418, Folder 2822)
  - Ecuador - Nursing, 1948; 02.1948/317.C
    - Ecuador, 1948 (Box 418, Folder 2822)
  - Guatemala, 1948; 02.1948/319
    - Guatemala, 1948 (Box 418, Folder 2822)
  - Guatemala - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 02.1948/319.R
    - Guatemala, 1948 (Box 418, Folder 2822)
  - Haiti, 1948; 02.1948/320
    - Haiti, 1948 (Box 418, Folder 2822)
  - Haiti - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 02.1948/320.R
    - Haiti, 1948 (Box 418, Folder 2822)
  - Honduras, 1948; 02.1948/321
    - Honduras, 1948 (Box 418, Folder 2822)
  - Mexico, 1948; 02.1948/323
    - Mexico - Administration, 1948 (Box 419, Folder 2823)
    - Mexico - (A-Z), 1948 (Box 419, Folder 2824)
  - Mexico - Medical Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/323.A
    - Mexico, 1948 (Box 419, Folder 2825)
  - Mexico - Nursing, 1948; 02.1948/323.C
    - Mexico, 1948 (Box 419, Folder 2825)
  - Mexico - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 02.1948/323.E
    - Mexico, 1948 (Box 419, Folder 2825)
  - Mexico - Humanities and Arts, 1948; 02.1948/323.R
    - Mexico, 1948 (Box 419, Folder 2825)
  - Nicaragua, 1948; 02.1948/325
    - Nicaragua, 1948 (Box 419, Folder 2826)
  - Panama, 1948; 02.1948/327
    - Panama, 1948 (Box 419, Folder 2826)
  - Paraguay, 1948; 02.1948/329
    - Paraguay, 1948 (Box 419, Folder 2826)
  - Peru, 1948; 02.1948/331
    - Peru, 1948 (Box 419, Folder 2827)
  - Peru - Medical Sciences, 1948; 02.1948/331.A
    - Peru, 1948 (Box 419, Folder 2828)
  - Peru - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 02.1948/331.E
    - Peru, 1948 (Box 419, Folder 2828)
  - Dominican Republic, 1948; 02.1948/335
    - Dominican Republic, 1948 (Box 419, Folder 2828)
  - Uruguay, 1948; 02.1948/337
  - Uruguay - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 02.1948/337.E
    - Uruguay, 1948 (Box 419, Folder 2828)
  - Venezuela, 1948; 02.1948/339
    - Venezuela, 1948 (Box 419, Folder 2829)
  - Venezuela - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1948; 02.1948/339.D
  - Venezuela - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1948; 02.1948/339.E